Raghvendra Singh Rathore

Salesforce Certified Application Architect with more than 10 years of consulting and development experience on Salesforce.com CRM and Force.com platform working with customers in Technology, Healthcare, Finance and Manufacturing sector. Skilled at analyzing business process and finding automated solution.

Excellent communication and interpersonal skills with strong ability in driving work force towards accomplishment of business and individual goals.

SKILLS

- Lightning components Aura and LWC
- Advanced Apex

- Automation using Process builders and Flows
- Agile software development life cycle

CERTIFICATIONS

Salesforce Certified Force.com Developer	Certification number: 1697539
Salesforce Certified Platform App Builder	Certification number: 16730617
Salesforce Certified Platform Developer I	Certification number: 18028847
Salesforce Certified Platform Developer II	Certification number: 19742783
Salesforce Certified Einstein Analytics and Discovery Consultant	Certification number: 21266748
Salesforce Certified Data Architecture and Management Designer	Certification number: 21008816
Salesforce Sharing And Visibility Designer	Certification number: 20497014
Salesforce Certified Application Architect	Certification number: 14006
Copado Certified Administrator	Certification number: 004645

WORK HISTORY

Specialist Master, Deloitte USI	Jun 2021 to Oct 2021	
Senior Consultant, Deloitte USI	Apr 2019 to May 2021	
Project Lead, Axtria Inc.	Sept 2015 to Apr 2019	
Sr. Software Developer, Vichara Technologies (I) Pvt. Ltd.	Nov 2012 to Sept 2015	
Software Developer, iBirds Services (P) Ltd.	May 2011 to Oct 2012	

EDUCATION

Year	Qualification	Institution	Percentage /CGPA
2011	Masters of Computer Applications	Punjab Technical University, Jalandhar	82
2010	Masters of Science-IT	Maharshi Dayanand Saraswati University, Ajmer	62.3

PROJECT SUMMARY

Project: CompSource Mutual

(Duration Jun 2021 to Till Date)

Description: CompSource Mutual is one of the leading workers' compensation insurance companies in

Oklahoma City, OK. **Role:** Technical Architect

Key Solutions:

- · Lead generation, Opportunity Submission, insurance policy and Claim intake process
- Experience Cloud (Customer Community for policyholders and partner community for agents)

Responsibilities:

- Implement ClaimVantage Leave management for SWA
- Project Discovery and Capability sizing
- Technical and functional grooming of user stories
- Prepare technical design and discuss with stakeholders on client side

Design environment strategy, deployment pipeline using Copado

Project: SWA LMO

(Duration Jun 2021 to Till Date)

Description: Southwest is one of the major airlines of the United States and the world's largest low-cost carrier airline based out of Dallas, TX.

Role: Technical Architect

Key Solutions:

- Implement ClaimVantage Leave management for SWA
- Experience Cloud (Customer Community)

Responsibilities:

- Project Discovery and Capability sizing
- Technical and functional grooming of user stories
- Prepare technical design and discuss with stakeholders on client side
- Design environment strategy, deployment pipeline using Copado

Project: Georgia Pacific

(Duration Feb 2020 to May 2021)

Description: Georgia-Pacific LLC is one of the world's largest manufacturers and distributors of building products based out of Atlanta, GA.

Role: Technical Lead

Key Solutions:

- Sales Cloud
- · Service Cloud
- Tableau CRM (Einstein Analytics)
- Experience Cloud (Customer Community)

Responsibilities:

- Project Discovery and Capability sizing
- Technical and functional grooming of user stories
- Prepare technical design and discuss with stakeholders on client side
- Lead development and QA team
- Design environment strategy, deployment pipeline using Copado

Project: Yeti Coolers CRM

(Duration April 2019 to Jan 2020)

Description: Yeti coolers a premium coolers and accessories manufacturer based out of Austin, TX.

Role: Lightning Developer

Responsibilities:

- Lightning Component Development and lead team of developers
- Setup continuous integration and manages Dev Ops
- REST based integration with SAP and PCI PAL

Project : Axtria SalesIQ™

(Duration March 2016 to April 2019)

Description: Axtria SalesIQ $^{\text{TM}}$ is a cloud based sales performance platform for flexible, high impact sales planning and operations. The integrated platform enables insight-driven territory alignment, call planning, incentive compensation and field reporting. Available on Salesforce App-Exchange.

Role: Technical Lead Responsibilities:

- R&D and Requirement gathering from business users
- · Designing the technical architecture of the product
- Development and lead team of developers
- Managed Salesforce security review process
- Integration with ESRI GIS APIs

Project: Incentive Compensation - MBO

(Duration September 2015 to February 2016)

Description: Incentive Compensation portal for self assessment, approval and calculate the quarterly payouts

for the field users. **Role:** Technical Lead

Responsibilities:

- Requirement gathering.
- Design the technical architecture of the application.
- Low level and High Level Design.
- Lead the team of 3 developers.

Project: OCM System build

(Duration November 2012 to August 2015)

Description: OCM is financial management company.

Role: Sr. Developer Responsibilities:

- Creation & implementation of Salesforce Customization
- Development using Visualforce pages, Apex classes, Apex Triggers
- Unit tests & code coverage
- Creation of Object/Fields/Page Layout
- Creating component using JQuery and Java script